# **STAN CHAO**

# (604) 700-5765 | Vancouver, BC cardioforcake.dev@gmail.com https://stanchao.netlify.app/

#### **Summary**

Nine years of successful sales and customer service experience in the financial services industry. In addition to my customer facing experience, I have a strong background in mathematics and finance through post-secondary and self-directed studies.

# **Skills**

❖ Critical Thinking
❖ Communication
❖ Research
❖ Team leadership
❖ Client relations
❖ Creativity

# **Work Experience**

#### Personal Banker | Bank of Montreal

12/2015-present

- Consistently ranked among the top 15% of investment advisors in my market
- Q3 2020, Q3 2019 and Q1 2017 internal Spotlight Award winner
- Experience with every area of retail banking, including lending and financial planning
- Excelled in cultivating relationships with clients to drive business growth
- Helped to train new personal bankers

#### **Customer Service Representative** | Bank of Montreal

04/2012-12/2015

- Consistently exceeded sales and customer service targets
- Excelled in resolving customer issues and complaints

#### **Energy Consultant** | Superior Energy

05/2009-09/2011

- Experience with cold calling and door-to-door sales
- Full commission-based compensation
- Trained new sales representatives

# **Education and Training**

Combined Major in Economics and Statistics   University of British Columbia	2013
Software Engineering Immersive   General Assembly	2021
Complete Python Bootcamp Certificate   Udemy.com	2021
Chartered Financial Analyst Level 1   CFA Institute	2018
Canadian Securities Course   Canadian Securities Institute	2016